A Guide to the Papers of Edwin M. Watson and of Frances Nash Watson, 9786
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Oversize Items
  - 2 photograph albums
    - George VI's U.S. Visit, June, 1939; F.D.R.'s fishing trip and inspection of Panama Canal, February 14-March 2, 1940.
    - Teheran and Cairo trips
- Phonograph Records
  - Phonograph album, "D-Day," June 6, 1944, P227. NBC, 4 records.